AS YOU STOOD BY
EUN-SU, HUI-SU AND JIN-PYO
Get ready.
Sure, do your worst.
Yes, I'm heading back right now.
Don't you dare!
No! No!
Why should he get to control your life?
If you don't leave him, you'll die.
The only thing that will end this
is if someone dies.
You're not gonna die.
If anyone's gonna die, it's Jin-pyo.
No! He can't see you! Eun-su! No!
Ah shit.
What a mess.
I shouldn't have done it.
Mistakes have consequences.
Wait!
Put that back on.
I won't embarrass you again--
Jin-pyo!
Wait!
I'll visit Mrs. Kim tomorrow
and beg for forgiveness.
I'll say it was my medication!
No one will know what goes on between us.
I'll fix everything.
Do you really think
that's anyone's concern?
Please don't!
I said I'll fix it!
Stay right there.
Don't come out, no matter what.
I can't just let him hurt you.
You said to do my worst?
Careful what you wish for.
You insulted a client
whose account could change my career,
so you'd better hope
the US market goes up tonight.
Since the markets usually go my way
the day after I teach you a lesson.
Sh!
Yes, sir?
No, I haven't been able to reach her.
I assume she has her phone off.
Right.
I already left her two.
It is rather late, sir.
Of course, sir.
I said shut it!
You have me apologizing to that idiot,
instead of celebrating
what should've been a win!
If Mrs. Kim decides to drop us,
my worst,
that you asked for,
will be worse than ever.
Hui-su.
You can't...
DEARLY DEPARTED
MS. KANG HUI-YEON
I'm sorry, Mrs. Kang.
Please help me.
Hui-su!
Hey!
Talk to me. Hui-su! Please!
I need to...
AMBULANCE
That's enough.
You need to... You need to wake up.
Come on!
Hey, you don't kill yourself.
You don't get to decide. You don't!
If you don't want me to do it...
...then get rid of that thing.
I'll put up with the beatings
when you lose control.
I am not gonna put up with
you treating me like a monkey in a zoo.
Get rid of it.
That is never gonna happen.
Stop!
No!
Drop it!
I'll do it.
I have to.
It won't be easy.
And even when it's done,
it won't be over.
But if we just...
EUN-SU
I'm in.
We can do this.
Dear residents,
this is an important message
from building management.
We would like to remind you that smoking
is prohibited in all indoor areas
and on private balconies.
We have received
numerous complaints about smoke
traveling through vents and windows.
Residents on higher floors
have been particularly inconvenienced,
and we ask that everyone respect
the nonsmoking rule.
Should we keep receiving complaints
about specific units,
we will need to meet with the residents
to resolve the matter.
Once again, building management
reminds you that smoking
is prohibited in all areas...
...and we ask that everyone respect
the nonsmoking rules.
I'm going!
If we keep receiving complaints
about specific units,
we will need to meet
with the residents to resolve the matter.
Once again, building management
reminds you that smoking is prohibited...
Screwdriver?
Yes. It's only about three inches.
I think I forgot to put it away
after I changed your strap.
Nope, I don't see it.
Uh, thanks, I guess I used it
to fix another watch after and forgot.
Is the new strap comfortable
and fitting right?
It's fine.
Oh, good.
What you said when I was here last,
I don't think it makes sense.
Which part?
She should've killed her husband.
Why did she die such an unfair death?
Yeah, so?
It's not worth killing him
if you end up in prison.
All the more reason not to get caught.
How do you kill someone
and not get caught?
Make sure no one knows you did it,
or make sure no one knows he's dead.
You watch way too many movies.
What can they do
if there's no body to prove it?
Why you asking?
Ah. You went to the funeral
and saw the husband there, didn't you?
Please don't!
Yeah.
Now I'm not gonna get any work done.
You're coming.
We'll go have the haejang-guk you owe me.
I have to get back to work.
I'm already late.
Hello, miss!
JINGANG CHINESE MARKET
- Mr. Jin, is there--
- Not right now.
Jang Kang.
Take that out first.
You're gonna need to do it in two trips.
I can make it all in one, sir.
I don't want you getting hurt
and stuck with a huge medical bill.
Do it in two, please.
Oh.
I didn't think of that. Thank you.
Did you need something?
I can go and have the soup
with you after all.
You didn't know
what I was gonna pull out, did ya?
Whoa, hey, hey!
- Um, my apologies, sir.
- Idiot!
He's pretty nervous.
Is he illegal?
Pretty much.
Where'd he come from?
Stowed away.
Without a passport?
Either he couldn't afford one,
or he had to run.
Probably no papers.
What can they do
if there's no body to prove it?
You're sure Jin-pyo doesn't have
any relatives in China? At all?
Positive.
This could work.
Excuse me, sir.
May I have a minute of your time?
That's a lot of money.
And all I'd do
is use a guy's passport
and fly to Shanghai?
It is quite a lot of money,
and the only condition
is that you don't ask any questions.
Just do as I say,
and you won't have any trouble
getting back to China.
I suppose you had to learn to keep quiet,
considering how you made your way here.
You can say no and keep scraping by,
hiding every time you see a cop car,
or go back home to your family
with a nice wad of cash in your pocket.
Think it over, Mr. Jang.
You'll be heading home in first class,
not smuggled in the hold of a ship.
Call me in three days with your answer.
You need it that soon?
Yeah.
Just one question.
It would really help me make a decision.
Is this person...
Is he alive?
He's alive. What are you talking about?
It's okay. He didn't notice.
I was freaked out
the second you guys walked in.
He looks so much like him.
I know. Luckily, he doesn't have
that same poker face.
From what I saw, he won't even
take the three days to answer.
But he seems like a decent guy, at least.
If we do this thing right,
Jin-pyo will go missing in China.
All we're missing is a reason for him
to get on a plane and head over there.
The person
you are trying to reach is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
MS. KIM MI-GYEONG
Hey.
How'd it go?
I'd say it went very well.
We should have her back here soon.
Great.
I wholeheartedly agree
with you, Mrs. Kim.
He's smart and hardworking,
and an excellent strategist.
Normally, I would stand by him 100%,
but the disrespect
he showed you that evening,
and on such an important occasion for you.
Please accept my deepest apologies.
I do hope you can see beyond
Mr. Noh's transgression and forgive us.
I would be honored if you allowed me to
put together a team of talented advisers.
They'll treat you and your valuable assets
with the respect they deserve.
I'll see to it myself.
Thank you, Mrs. Kim.
We won't let you down.
Yes, you too.
Uh, yes, that's our motto.
Bye, now.
CLIENT PROFILE
KIM MI-GYEONG
Lavie Department Store?
DOWNLOAD COMPLETE
I thought we could go out
for a nice dinner.
You can even choose your own outfit.
I'll wait for you here.
You made a good choice.
Pretty, and it covers up
all the right places.
Good to see you, Eun-su.
Good to see you too.
Oh, thank you.
Hui-su.
Hi, Eun-su.
You haven't seen each other in a while,
so I thought I'd surprise you both.
I think it worked.
Sure did.
You're glad, aren't you?
Yes, thanks.
Over here.
Here's to seeing you away from work, hmm?
Right.
And...
...here's to the girl we love.
Oh no! I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Your jacket. It's all soaked.
I got you everywhere.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry. What a mess.
It's fine. It's not that bad.
- You called, sir?
- Yes, I spilled a glass of wine.
I can help you with that, ma'am.
It's fine.
You should go with her.
We'll wait for you to order.
Okay, I'll try to make it quick.
What's new?
You know, I should check on Hui-su.
The closet.
You were there that night.
I think what you heard
might have given you the wrong idea.
Hui-su
is pretty sick.
She struggles.
Her mother's situation hit her hard.
And after the miscarriage,
she gave up writing altogether.
Ever since, she's been anxious
and having dark thoughts.
I had to install a monitor
to make sure she's okay when I'm gone.
She thinks I wanted to spy on her.
I'm worried.
I think she's having a breakdown.
The beatings can't be helping that.
Some things need to stay
between husband and wife.
Violence is private, huh?
If you had love in your life,
you would understand.
Hui-su would die if we weren't together.
And I'd be lost without her too.
That's what marriage is.
So having love means
having to get beaten, is that it?
I'd watch it if I were you.
'Cause when I get challenged,
your friend gets hurt.
You'll be taking it out on her
again tonight, won't you?
Did I tell you I found a way
to smooth things over with Mrs. Kim?
I don't have to go see her?
Turns out,
she and Eun-su have a connection.
I'm always amazed
at what a small world this is.
Such a happy coincidence.
Hui-su has been quite troubled by this,
so I take it you will step in to help?
MS. KIM MI-GYEONG
CHEONGDAM-DONG
HOPES TO HOLD SOLO EXHIBITION
BEFORE TURNING 60
I've always wanted
to see your first piece.
It's such an honor to see it here
in your studio, Mrs. Kim.
Compared to what you did for me back then,
this is nothing.
I don't know if I did much,
seeing as I had just started that job.
I only ran as fast as I could
to impress my boss.
You got there ahead of both the tow truck
and the police. You saved me.
My mother-in-law
betrayed me viciously that day.
If it weren't for you,
I would've been left freezing in
the middle of that terrible neighborhood.
Utterly depressed and wanting to die.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Mrs. Kim.
You said if I ever need a favor?
Pardon me, where's the restroom?
Thank you
for agreeing to see me again.
You should
save your gratitude for Ms. Jo.
I will accept your apology
and consider the matter closed,
so this conversation's over.
And please stop calling.
That's what you decided to do
with the one favor I owed you?
I expected something bigger.
It's always been a dream of yours,
hasn't it?
Putting on a solo exhibit
before you turn 60?
You remember that?
I wish my mom
could have a life like yours,
full of dreams and big ideas.
I thought how nice it must be when you can
spend your days pursuing your passion.
I'll take over from here.
Sorry, Mrs. Kim.
I didn't know you were coming today.
Huh.
You will ensure that none of this
gets back to my husband.
And I... want nothing linked directly to me.
Yes. We'll use utmost discretion.
Our most important clients
do prefer a quieter approach.
Rest assured, we'll protect your privacy.
If you do not cross the line,
Hui-su will not get hurt.
Marital affairs are best
left between husband and wife.
I know it hasn't been a month already.
You're not open today,
so it doesn't count as gym time.
Go. Come back in a month.
Or not at all, for all I care.
I need this place.
You won't even know I'm there. I swear.
SOGANG UNIVERSITY, ECHO, JO EUN-SU
MR. JANG KANG
Hello?
Hi.
The passport thing?
I'll do it.
You're willing to go back to China?
Yes.
I miss my son.
Thank you.
I finished my run, sir.
Did I see you getting out of a car?
Yeah.
A friend from home is in town.
Hey!
A friend from back home, huh?
Must have been nice.
- Yeah.
- Good.
You can go.
Using Mrs. Kim's account?
Since your husband requested the meeting,
it's the best way to avoid suspicion.
Oh.
I feel bad knowing
that she'll lose money on this.
We didn't have a choice.
Although, the firm will help her.
They'll be able to cover it,
and more importantly,
make sure it stays quiet.
She's a strong woman.
She's gotten over worse.
I see Jang. We'll talk later.
Oh.
I was so surprised when I looked
in the mirror. I barely recognized myself.
I guess, uh,
I'll get used to it.
You do look really good.
- Oh, let me.
- Ah.
I can take that.
Wow, all this?
Uh, tilt your head a little. Bend down.
Oh. There was something in my hair, huh?
Uh... Oh, here too.
Pull over.
Captain! We're gonna be late!
It'll help if you use the siren.
Right.
Is everything all right?
No, we're good.
Jin-pyo,
the Presidential Office evaluation
is coming up soon.
CHOI WON-HO
We should be there in five.
I'll let you know what's happening
when we get there.
MINE
BREEZEHILL, 42-78
APGUJEONG-RO, GANGNAM-GU, SEOUL
Looks like I'll get promoted
before my sister even gets evaluated.
Have you gotten
even more beautiful?
Is there something going on
that's making you glow like this?
I would tell you, of course.
Good, because I don't like secrets.
Such a good girl.
Turns me on.
Which one do you want
for your company dinner?
He tends to drink more than usual
at his monthly branch dinners.
And even more when he gets home.
Then he passes out for the night.
You fly out on Friday.
We booked all your tickets.
I thought I'd have longer.
Sorry if this is catching you
on short notice,
but I figured you could move fast.
You figured that right.
I don't have much.
I'll give you the flight details
when we have everything worked out.
"We"?
You know, me and the other guy.
Oh.
Right.
Your first half of the payment.
Your son must have really missed his dad.
There's a bit extra in there
for you to take care of
your wife and son's travel expenses
to meet you at the airport.
Here.
Oh, thanks, Kang.
MS. JO EUN-SU
Have you noticed
his new haircut and fancy clothes?
I think he has a girlfriend.
He says he's heading back to China.
Who?
Jang Kang, sir.
I guess he saved enough to get home.
Get yourself ready
as quietly as possible,
and watch out for Mr. Jin.
Not much gets by that guy.
Be careful not to let on.
Yeah.
The gym's closed for the day,
and you only suspended me
from attending classes.
Isn't that right, sir?
You've never gotten past white belt
all these years.
Do you ever wonder why that is?
From the moment you entered the gym,
it was obvious that your reason
for being here...
...stemmed from desperation.
I gave you the worst-smelling partners,
and you didn't back off.
I denied you opportunities to advance,
and you refused to quit.
I just wanted to try to improve.
JO EUN-SU
Are you serious?
Jo Eun-su.
This was your last day here.
Take care of yourself.
Can I go with Eun-su
and visit my mother a little later?
What for?
She wants to bring her flowers
and say hello.
You can go.
And I'll be here when you get home.
I know that.
Tomorrow,
we'll have to do this without GPS.
Hmm.
MINE
- Hello, Mr. Noh.
- Hello, ma'am.
- How are you?
- Fine. How are you?
Yes, thanks. Did we have an appointment?
I don't seem to have you on my schedule.
- No, we were just in the neighborhood.
- What a nice surprise. Have a seat.
Good to see you.
We're almost there.
Who else thinks
our deputy branch manager
should say a few words
to celebrate closing such a big deal, huh?
- No speeches, please.
- Noh Jin-pyo.
Noh Jin-pyo!
I just did my job.
I appreciate it, but I can't.
- Noh Jin-pyo! Noh Jin-pyo!
- Come on.
Noh Jin-pyo!
Noh Jin-pyo! Noh Jin-pyo!
- Yeah!
- Speech!
I'm sure some of you
would have loved to see me crash and burn,
even though your bonuses
all depend on this deal.
For those of you who thought a nice
corner office might become available,
rest assured
that Noh Jin-pyo
is here to stay.
For good.
I fought for all of you.
For the future of Golden One!
- To us!
- Yeah!
SAN 1, DAECHI-RI, HYEONBUK-MYEON,
YANGYANG-GUN, GANGWON-DO
Where the hell did you go?
That's no nursing home.
MR. NOH JIN-PYO,
YOU HAVEN'T BOOKED ACCOMMODATIONS
YOUR TRIP IS COMING UP, MR. NOH JIN-PYO!
HURRY BEFORE YOUR SHANGHAI HOTEL
DISCOUNT EXPIRES!